<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</title>
    <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/media/icon_hu08a0612ece3264b0c60a561067d923a4_34621_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Event</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/event/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/event/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further event details, including page elements such as image galleries, can be added to the body of this page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RegTrack: Uncovering Global Disparities in Third-party Advertising and Tracking</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2026-madweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2026-madweb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Havoc Paradox in Generator-Based Fuzzing</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-tosem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-tosem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminars</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/seminars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/seminars/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward Practical and Usable Provenance-based Intrusion Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenix-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenix-login/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRBlock: A Large-Scale Measurement Study of the Great Firewall of Iran</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025_usenixsec_irblock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025_usenixsec_irblock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Great Firewall of Iran (GFI) has evolved significantly over the past decade,
constantly adding sophisticated blocking techniques. Prior research into Iran&amp;rsquo;s
Internet censorship, however, has primarily been one-off studies, leaving
significant gaps in understanding the breadth and evolution of its filtering
strategies. Exploiting the bidirectional blocking behaviors of the GFI and its
own injection mechanisms as a side-channel to determine traffic disruption, we
developed IRBlock, a novel large-scale, multi-protocol measurement system
designed to measure DNS, HTTP, and UDP-based censorship across Iran, enabling
continuous monitoring and in-depth exploration of the GFI&amp;rsquo;s blocking behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over a period of 2.5 months, IRBlock has periodically measured the entire Iran&amp;rsquo;s
IP address space and tested the blocking status of over 500M apex domains,
uncovering new insights into the GFI&amp;rsquo;s censorship practices of different core
network protocols. Notably, IRBlock identified 6.8M IPs subjected to DNS
poisoning and HTTP blockpage injection, and 5.4M IPs subjected to UDP-based
traffic disruption. We also analyzed the censored domains found by IRBlock and
discovered over censored 6M FQDNs and 3.3M apex domains. Via reverse engineering
of the GFI&amp;rsquo;s blocking rules, we found many domains are inadvertently overblocked
due to blanket blocking policies of entire TLDs (e.g., .il), resulting in large
collateral damage to innocuous websites. We also find that the GFI&amp;rsquo;s blocking
strategies show many similarities to those observed for the Great Firewall of
China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our study represents the most comprehensive view of Iran&amp;rsquo;s Internet censorship
to date. Leveraging IRBlock&amp;rsquo;s data, we shed light on the GFI&amp;rsquo;s evolving
filtering strategies and the challenges faced by circumvention tools. We discuss
the implications of our findings on existing censorship measurement and
circumvention efforts. We hope that the insights gained from our study can
inform not only the research community but also policymakers and activists
working to promote digital freedom in Iran and beyond. All data collected by
IRBlock will be made publicly available to facilitate further research on
nation-state censorship and Internet freedom advocacy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORTHRUS: Achieving High Quality of Attribution in Provenance-based Intrusion Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenixsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenixsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_FpCefZeObw?si=sXcdMnS2nWki-uJF&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relocate-Vote: Using Sparsity Information to Exploit Ciphertext Side-Channels</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenixsec_relocatevote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenixsec_relocatevote/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Simpler is Better: A Comprehensive Analysis of State-of-the-Art Provenance-Based Intrusion Detection Systems</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenixsec-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-usenixsec-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Or_iAucWqT4?si=E1OlKsDU3fAZRM8p&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Thompson Sampling and UCB: Towards More Efficient Trade-offs Between Privacy and Regret</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-icml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-icml/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/courses/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growlithe: A Developer-Centric Compliance Tool for Serverless Applications</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-sp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-sp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;!--
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iNaucHm7Z6w&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
--&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Nobody There? Good! Globally Measuring Connection Tampering without Responsive Endhosts</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-sp-mint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-sp-mint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many techniques have been introduced to measure network interference-tampering
performed by nation-state censors or corporate firewalls to block unwanted
traffic. However, virtually all prior measurement techniques require some degree
of participation from endpoints within each country of study: including VPNs,
cloud providers, or volunteers willing to run measurement software on their
personal devices at their own risk. However, such endpoints are not always
available in all countries that tamper with connections, leaving many networks
unmeasurable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we present the first global, active, network interference
measurements that require no participating end-points within any country of
study. Our techniques extend two recent studies that use packet sequences that
trigger network interference from outside the country of study by tricking
middleboxes into believing a connection exists. Our system, Mint, generalizes
and automates this approach-which had previously only been applied to two
countries-to allow it to apply to the global IPv4 and IPv6 Internet. We use Mint
to conduct the first global measurements of network interference without using
any participating endpoints, and the first comprehensive scans of IPv6
interference. We show that we are able to measure networks, autonomous systems,
and even entire countries that previous methods could not. We also present
several case studies that highlight how our tool can be used to perform new
measurement studies of network interference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DPack: Efficiency-Oriented Privacy Budget Scheduling</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-eurosys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-eurosys/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Reproducibility of Provenance-based Intrusion Detection that uses Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-rep/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Randomized Smoothing: Certified Adversarial Robustness for Multi-Step Defences</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-neurips-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-neurips-2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panoramia: Privacy auditing of machine learning models without retraining</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-neurips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-neurips/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Monster: Efficient On-device Budgeting for Differentially-Private Ad-Measurement Systems</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-sosp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-sosp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SafeBPF: Hardware-assisted Defense-in-depth for eBPF Kernel Extensions</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-ccsw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-ccsw/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GFWeb: Measuring the Great Firewall&#39;s Web Censorship at Scale</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_usenixsec_gfweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_usenixsec_gfweb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Censorship systems such as the Great Firewall (GFW) have been continuously
refined to enhance their filtering capabilities. However, most prior
studies, and in particular the GFW, have been limited in scope and
conducted over short time periods, leading to gaps in our understanding of
the GFW&amp;rsquo;s evolving Web censorship mechanisms over time. We introduce GFWeb,
a novel system designed to discover domain blocklists used by the GFW for
censoring Web access. GFWeb exploits GFW&amp;rsquo;s bidirectional and loss-tolerant
blocking behavior to enable testing hundreds of millions of domains on a
monthly basis, thereby facilitating large-scale longitudinal measurement of
HTTP and HTTPS blocking mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the course of 20 months, GFWeb has tested a total of 1.02 billion
domains, and detected 943K and 55K pay-level domains censored by the GFW&amp;rsquo;s
HTTP and HTTPS filters, respectively. To the best of our knowledge, our
study represents the most extensive set of domains censored by the GFW ever
discovered to date, many of which have never been detected by prior
systems. Analyzing the longitudinal dataset collected by GFWeb, we observe
that the GFW has been upgraded to mitigate several issues previously
identified by the research community, including overblocking and failure in
reassembling fragmented packets. More importantly, we discover that the
GFW&amp;rsquo;s bidirectional blocking is not symmetric as previously thought, i.e.,
it can only be triggered by certain domains when probed from inside the
country. We discuss the implications of our work on existing censorship
measurement and circumvention efforts. We hope insights gained from our
study can help inform future research, especially in monitoring censorship
and developing new evasion tools.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NetShaper: A Differentially Private Network Side-Channel Mitigation System</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-usenixsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-usenixsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;!--
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iNaucHm7Z6w&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
--&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Generation of Web Censorship Probe Lists</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_popets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_popets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Domain probe lists&amp;mdash;used to determine which URLs to probe for Web
censorship&amp;mdash;play a critical role in Internet censorship measurement
studies. Indeed, the size and accuracy of the domain probe list limits the
set of censored pages that can be detected; inaccurate lists can lead to an
incomplete view of the censorship landscape or biased results. Previous
efforts to generate domain probe lists have been mostly manual or
crowdsourced. This approach is time-consuming, prone to errors, and does
not scale well to the ever-changing censorship landscape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we explore methods for automatically generating probe lists
that are both comprehensive and up-to-date for Web censorship measurement.
We start from an initial set of 139,957 unique URLs from various existing
test lists consisting of pages from a variety of languages to generate new
candidate pages. By analyzing content from these URLs (i.e., performing
topic and keyword extraction), expanding these topics, and using them as a
feed to search engines, our method produces 119,255 new URLs across 35,147
domains. We then test the new candidate pages by attempting to access each
URL from servers in eleven different global locations over a span of four
months to check for their connectivity and potential signs of censorship.
Our measurements reveal that our method discovered over 1,400 domains&amp;mdash;not
present in the original dataset&amp;mdash;we suspect to be blocked. In short,
automatically updating probe lists is possible, and can help further
automate censorship measurements at scale.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward Automated DNS Tampering Detection Using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_foci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_foci/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DNS manipulation is one of the most prevalent and effective techniques for
censoring Internet access and interfering with users&amp;rsquo; online activities
worldwide. Reliable detection of DNS tampering is crucial, but challenging
due to evolving censorship tactics and the lack of complete ground truth
data. In this paper, we demonstrate the power of machine learning (ML) in
addressing these challenges by applying supervised and unsupervised models
to recent global DNS measurement data collected by the Open Observatory of
Network Interference (OONI). Our models achieve high accuracy in learning
expert-defined heuristics for DNS tampering and uncovering new manipulation
instances missed by rule-based approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through an extensive analysis evaluating different training data volumes
and time windows from one to 24 months, we provide key insights into how
the quantity and diversity of data, as well as evolving censorship
behaviors, impact model performance over time. Remarkably, our ML detector
can enhance traditional heuristics by accurately identifying DNS
fingerprints with high confidence. These findings underscore the
effectiveness of ML techniques in detecting global DNS manipulation at
scale while adapting to emerging censorship tactics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To foster future research, we will release our regularly updated models,
enabling the development of robust, sustainable censorship detection
systems capable of withstanding the dynamic landscape of Internet
censorship worldwide. Our work paves the way for more proactive
interventions that safeguard Internet freedom globally.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KAIROS: Practical Intrusion Detection and Investigation using Whole-system Provenance</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-sp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-sp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turbo: Effective Caching in Differentially-Private Databases</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-aaai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024-aaai/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turbo: Effective Caching in Differentially-Private Databases</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2023-sosp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2023-sosp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Unprivileged eBPF Potential with Dynamic Sandboxing</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2023-sigcomm-ebpf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2023-sigcomm-ebpf/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Effect of Training Data on Deep Learning Predictions via Randomized Experiments</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2022-icml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2022-icml/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DP-Adam: Correcting DP Bias in Adam&#39;s Second Moment Estimation</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2023-rtml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2023-rtml/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/tour/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacer: Comprehensive Network Side-Channel Mitigation in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2022-usenixsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2022-usenixsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;!--
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iNaucHm7Z6w&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
--&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Namespaced Kernel Audit for Containers</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2021-socc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2021-socc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4S7dr4a_Da0&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIGL: Securing Software Installations Through Deep Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2021-usenixsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2021-usenixsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iNaucHm7Z6w&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jian Yang and Monica Hall Win the Best Paper Award at Wowchemy 2020</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/post/20-12-02-icml-best-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/post/20-12-02-icml-best-paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to Jian Yang and Monica Hall for winning the Best Paper Award at the 2020 Conference on Wowchemy for their paper “Learning Wowchemy”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Integer tempus augue non tempor egestas. Proin nisl nunc, dignissim in accumsan dapibus, auctor ullamcorper neque. Quisque at elit felis. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia curae; Aenean eget elementum odio. Cras interdum eget risus sit amet aliquet. In volutpat, nisl ut fringilla dignissim, arcu nisl suscipit ante, at accumsan sapien nisl eu eros.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sed eu dui nec ligula bibendum dapibus. Nullam imperdiet auctor tortor, vel cursus mauris malesuada non. Quisque ultrices euismod dapibus. Aenean sed gravida risus. Sed nisi tortor, vulputate nec quam non, placerat porta nisl. Nunc varius lobortis urna, condimentum facilisis ipsum molestie eu. Ut molestie eleifend ligula sed dignissim. Duis ut tellus turpis. Praesent tincidunt, nunc sed congue malesuada, mauris enim maximus massa, eget interdum turpis urna et ante. Morbi sem nisl, cursus quis mollis et, interdum luctus augue. Aliquam laoreet, leo et accumsan tincidunt, libero neque aliquet lectus, a ultricies lorem mi a orci.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mauris dapibus sem vel magna convallis laoreet. Donec in venenatis urna, vitae sodales odio. Praesent tortor diam, varius non luctus nec, bibendum vel est. Quisque id sem enim. Maecenas at est leo. Vestibulum tristique pellentesque ex, blandit placerat nunc eleifend sit amet. Fusce eget lectus bibendum, accumsan mi quis, luctus sem. Etiam vitae nulla scelerisque, eleifend odio in, euismod quam. Etiam porta ullamcorper massa, vitae gravida turpis euismod quis. Mauris sodales sem ac ultrices viverra. In placerat ultrices sapien. Suspendisse eu arcu hendrerit, luctus tortor cursus, maximus dolor. Proin et velit et quam gravida dapibus. Donec blandit justo ut consequat tristique.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Hendricks Wins First Place in the Wowchemy Prize</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/post/20-12-01-wowchemy-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/post/20-12-01-wowchemy-prize/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to Richard Hendricks for winning first place in the Wowchemy Prize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Integer tempus augue non tempor egestas. Proin nisl nunc, dignissim in accumsan dapibus, auctor ullamcorper neque. Quisque at elit felis. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia curae; Aenean eget elementum odio. Cras interdum eget risus sit amet aliquet. In volutpat, nisl ut fringilla dignissim, arcu nisl suscipit ante, at accumsan sapien nisl eu eros.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sed eu dui nec ligula bibendum dapibus. Nullam imperdiet auctor tortor, vel cursus mauris malesuada non. Quisque ultrices euismod dapibus. Aenean sed gravida risus. Sed nisi tortor, vulputate nec quam non, placerat porta nisl. Nunc varius lobortis urna, condimentum facilisis ipsum molestie eu. Ut molestie eleifend ligula sed dignissim. Duis ut tellus turpis. Praesent tincidunt, nunc sed congue malesuada, mauris enim maximus massa, eget interdum turpis urna et ante. Morbi sem nisl, cursus quis mollis et, interdum luctus augue. Aliquam laoreet, leo et accumsan tincidunt, libero neque aliquet lectus, a ultricies lorem mi a orci.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mauris dapibus sem vel magna convallis laoreet. Donec in venenatis urna, vitae sodales odio. Praesent tortor diam, varius non luctus nec, bibendum vel est. Quisque id sem enim. Maecenas at est leo. Vestibulum tristique pellentesque ex, blandit placerat nunc eleifend sit amet. Fusce eget lectus bibendum, accumsan mi quis, luctus sem. Etiam vitae nulla scelerisque, eleifend odio in, euismod quam. Etiam porta ullamcorper massa, vitae gravida turpis euismod quis. Mauris sodales sem ac ultrices viverra. In placerat ultrices sapien. Suspendisse eu arcu hendrerit, luctus tortor cursus, maximus dolor. Proin et velit et quam gravida dapibus. Donec blandit justo ut consequat tristique.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNICORN: Runtime Provenance-Based Detector for Advanced Persistent Threats</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2020-ndss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2020-ndss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/B9ACkb320s0&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runtime Analysis of Whole-System Provenance</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2018-ccs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2018-ccs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6VBVwH88o4Y&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Whole-System Provenance Capture</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2017-socc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2017-socc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
