<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonas Tai | UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</title>
    <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/jonas-tai/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/jonas-tai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Jonas Tai</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/media/icon_hu08a0612ece3264b0c60a561067d923a4_34621_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Jonas Tai</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/jonas-tai/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRBlock: A Large-Scale Measurement Study of the Great Firewall of Iran</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025_usenixsec_irblock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025_usenixsec_irblock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Great Firewall of Iran (GFI) has evolved significantly over the past decade,
constantly adding sophisticated blocking techniques. Prior research into Iran&amp;rsquo;s
Internet censorship, however, has primarily been one-off studies, leaving
significant gaps in understanding the breadth and evolution of its filtering
strategies. Exploiting the bidirectional blocking behaviors of the GFI and its
own injection mechanisms as a side-channel to determine traffic disruption, we
developed IRBlock, a novel large-scale, multi-protocol measurement system
designed to measure DNS, HTTP, and UDP-based censorship across Iran, enabling
continuous monitoring and in-depth exploration of the GFI&amp;rsquo;s blocking behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over a period of 2.5 months, IRBlock has periodically measured the entire Iran&amp;rsquo;s
IP address space and tested the blocking status of over 500M apex domains,
uncovering new insights into the GFI&amp;rsquo;s censorship practices of different core
network protocols. Notably, IRBlock identified 6.8M IPs subjected to DNS
poisoning and HTTP blockpage injection, and 5.4M IPs subjected to UDP-based
traffic disruption. We also analyzed the censored domains found by IRBlock and
discovered over censored 6M FQDNs and 3.3M apex domains. Via reverse engineering
of the GFI&amp;rsquo;s blocking rules, we found many domains are inadvertently overblocked
due to blanket blocking policies of entire TLDs (e.g., .il), resulting in large
collateral damage to innocuous websites. We also find that the GFI&amp;rsquo;s blocking
strategies show many similarities to those observed for the Great Firewall of
China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our study represents the most comprehensive view of Iran&amp;rsquo;s Internet censorship
to date. Leveraging IRBlock&amp;rsquo;s data, we shed light on the GFI&amp;rsquo;s evolving
filtering strategies and the challenges faced by circumvention tools. We discuss
the implications of our findings on existing censorship measurement and
circumvention efforts. We hope that the insights gained from our study can
inform not only the research community but also policymakers and activists
working to promote digital freedom in Iran and beyond. All data collected by
IRBlock will be made publicly available to facilitate further research on
nation-state censorship and Internet freedom advocacy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
