<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>D. Levin | UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</title>
    <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/d.-levin/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/d.-levin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>D. Levin</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/media/icon_hu08a0612ece3264b0c60a561067d923a4_34621_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>D. Levin</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/d.-levin/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Nobody There? Good! Globally Measuring Connection Tampering without Responsive Endhosts</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-sp-mint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-sp-mint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many techniques have been introduced to measure network interference-tampering
performed by nation-state censors or corporate firewalls to block unwanted
traffic. However, virtually all prior measurement techniques require some degree
of participation from endpoints within each country of study: including VPNs,
cloud providers, or volunteers willing to run measurement software on their
personal devices at their own risk. However, such endpoints are not always
available in all countries that tamper with connections, leaving many networks
unmeasurable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we present the first global, active, network interference
measurements that require no participating end-points within any country of
study. Our techniques extend two recent studies that use packet sequences that
trigger network interference from outside the country of study by tricking
middleboxes into believing a connection exists. Our system, Mint, generalizes
and automates this approach-which had previously only been applied to two
countries-to allow it to apply to the global IPv4 and IPv6 Internet. We use Mint
to conduct the first global measurements of network interference without using
any participating endpoints, and the first comprehensive scans of IPv6
interference. We show that we are able to measure networks, autonomous systems,
and even entire countries that previous methods could not. We also present
several case studies that highlight how our tool can be used to perform new
measurement studies of network interference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
