<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 | UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</title>
    <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication-type/2/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication-type/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>2</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/media/icon_hu08a0612ece3264b0c60a561067d923a4_34621_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>2</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication-type/2/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Havoc Paradox in Generator-Based Fuzzing</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-tosem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2025-tosem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Generation of Web Censorship Probe Lists</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_popets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_popets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Domain probe lists&amp;mdash;used to determine which URLs to probe for Web
censorship&amp;mdash;play a critical role in Internet censorship measurement
studies. Indeed, the size and accuracy of the domain probe list limits the
set of censored pages that can be detected; inaccurate lists can lead to an
incomplete view of the censorship landscape or biased results. Previous
efforts to generate domain probe lists have been mostly manual or
crowdsourced. This approach is time-consuming, prone to errors, and does
not scale well to the ever-changing censorship landscape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we explore methods for automatically generating probe lists
that are both comprehensive and up-to-date for Web censorship measurement.
We start from an initial set of 139,957 unique URLs from various existing
test lists consisting of pages from a variety of languages to generate new
candidate pages. By analyzing content from these URLs (i.e., performing
topic and keyword extraction), expanding these topics, and using them as a
feed to search engines, our method produces 119,255 new URLs across 35,147
domains. We then test the new candidate pages by attempting to access each
URL from servers in eleven different global locations over a span of four
months to check for their connectivity and potential signs of censorship.
Our measurements reveal that our method discovered over 1,400 domains&amp;mdash;not
present in the original dataset&amp;mdash;we suspect to be blocked. In short,
automatically updating probe lists is possible, and can help further
automate censorship measurements at scale.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
