<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>S Cho | UBC Security &amp; Privacy Group</title>
    <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/s-cho/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/s-cho/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>S Cho</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/media/icon_hu08a0612ece3264b0c60a561067d923a4_34621_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>S Cho</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/author/s-cho/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward Automated DNS Tampering Detection Using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_foci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://spg.cs.ubc.ca/publication/2024_foci/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DNS manipulation is one of the most prevalent and effective techniques for
censoring Internet access and interfering with users&amp;rsquo; online activities
worldwide. Reliable detection of DNS tampering is crucial, but challenging
due to evolving censorship tactics and the lack of complete ground truth
data. In this paper, we demonstrate the power of machine learning (ML) in
addressing these challenges by applying supervised and unsupervised models
to recent global DNS measurement data collected by the Open Observatory of
Network Interference (OONI). Our models achieve high accuracy in learning
expert-defined heuristics for DNS tampering and uncovering new manipulation
instances missed by rule-based approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through an extensive analysis evaluating different training data volumes
and time windows from one to 24 months, we provide key insights into how
the quantity and diversity of data, as well as evolving censorship
behaviors, impact model performance over time. Remarkably, our ML detector
can enhance traditional heuristics by accurately identifying DNS
fingerprints with high confidence. These findings underscore the
effectiveness of ML techniques in detecting global DNS manipulation at
scale while adapting to emerging censorship tactics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To foster future research, we will release our regularly updated models,
enabling the development of robust, sustainable censorship detection
systems capable of withstanding the dynamic landscape of Internet
censorship worldwide. Our work paves the way for more proactive
interventions that safeguard Internet freedom globally.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
